<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Awais Mustafa</title>
    <link>http://awaismustafa.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Awais Mustafa</description>
    <image>
      <title>Awais Mustafa</title>
      <url>http://awaismustafa.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://awaismustafa.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 11:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://awaismustafa.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>All My Certificates</title>
      <link>http://awaismustafa.com/blog/certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://awaismustafa.com/blog/certification/</guid>
      <description>AWS Specialization Certificate Description AWS Cloud Technical Essentials Learn how to use several AWS compute services, including Amazon EC2, AWS Lambda, and Amazon ECS. AWS: Migrating to the Cloud Learn how to migrate to the cloud. It means moving computer stuff to the internet, which can save money and improve performance. AWS Fundamentals: Building Serverless Applications Learn how to build serverless applications on AWS. Linkedin Learning Certificate Description Verification Linkedin: Learning Terraform Learn Terraform which is a DevOps tool for infrastructure as code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFS Server: A Complete Guide to Setting Up and Configuring</title>
      <link>http://awaismustafa.com/blog/nfssetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://awaismustafa.com/blog/nfssetup/</guid>
      <description>NFS Setup Guide in 2 minutes by Awais Mustafa</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little bit About My Website</title>
      <link>http://awaismustafa.com/blog/littlebit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://awaismustafa.com/blog/littlebit/</guid>
      <description>Highligthing the result I intend to place the results of various works on this webpage, highlighting the results of mini projects, ongoing projects, and more. So, for those who are reading, thank you!
All of the work that I have been doing over the year,and months been extremely fun, eye opening, and a great experience altogether! #comments About Me A little bit about me. I love watching TV; Hopefully, that doesn&amp;rsquo;t scare you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
